http://www.socaluncensored.com/privacy-policy/

TwitterInstagramFacebookYouTubeHome Privacy PolicySoCalUncensored.com (“SoCalUncensored.com“) operates SoCalUncensored.com and may operate other websites. It is SoCalUncensored.com’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.Website VisitorsLike most website operators, SoCalUncensored.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. SoCalUncensored.com’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how SoCalUncensored.com’s visitors use its website. From time to time, SoCalUncensored.com may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.SoCalUncensored.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on SoCalUncensored.com blogs/sites. SoCalUncensored.com only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.Gathering of Personally-Identifying InformationCertain visitors to SoCalUncensored.com’s websites choose to interact with SoCalUncensored.com in ways that require SoCalUncensored.com to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that SoCalUncensored.com gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at SoCalUncensored.comto provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with SoCalUncensored.com are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, SoCalUncensored.com collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with SoCalUncensored.com. SoCalUncensored.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.CookiesA cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. SoCalUncensored.com uses cookies to help SoCalUncensored.com identify and track visitors, their usage of SoCalUncensored.com website, and their website access preferences. If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year. SoCalUncensored.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using SoCalUncensored.com’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of SoCalUncensored.com’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.Aggregated StatisticsSoCalUncensored.com may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. SoCalUncensored.com may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, SoCalUncensored.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying InformationSoCalUncensored.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on SoCalUncensored.com’s behalf or to provide services available at SoCalUncensored.com’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using SoCalUncensored.com’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. SoCalUncensored.com will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, SoCalUncensored.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when SoCalUncensored.com believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of SoCalUncensored.com, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an SoCalUncensored.com website and have supplied your email address, SoCalUncensored.com may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with SoCalUncensored.com and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. SoCalUncensored.com takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.How long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.Business TransfersIf SoCalUncensored.com, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that SoCalUncensored.com goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of SoCalUncensored.com may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.AdsAds appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by SoCalUncensored.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.As an Amazon Associate we earn from qualifying purchases.Privacy Policy ChangesAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, SoCalUncensored.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in SoCalUncensored.com’s sole discretion. SoCalUncensored.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a SoCalUncensored.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.Contact informationFor privacy-specific concerns contact steve@socaluncensored.com.
Featured LinksEvents Calendar: A list of pro-wrestling and MMA events happening throughout Southern California.SoCalUNCENSORED’s Rankings: Our monthly rankings have returned!Highspots The leading provider of pro-wrestling and MMA merchandise. From wrestling boots to wrestling DVD’s, wrestling action figures to title belts.PromotionsAlternative Wrestling Show Baja Stars USA Bar Wrestling Championship Wrestling from Hollywood Empire Wrestling Federation Ground Zero Knokx Pro Entertainment Lucha Underground Lucha Va Voom Maverick Pro Millennium Pro Wrestling PCW Ultra Pro Wrestling Guerrilla Santino Bros. Wrestling Academy SoCal Pro Wrestling Underground Empire Wrestling Vendetta Pro Wrestling Venue Wrestling EntertainmentFollow us on TwitterMy Tweets
